AAA Bank Fixed Deposit In today's video,
we will talk about AAA Bank FD.
If you want to
earn good returns by investing your money safely,
then AAA Bank FD can be a good option.
In this video, we will also
learn how much return you will get if you invest ₹5000000
in an III Bank FD for 1 year. So,
you must watch this video completely. So let's
start this video. First of all, if
we talk about III Bank Fixed Deposit interest
rate, then this is the
new interest rate of AAA Bank Fixed Deposit. Here AAA
Bank is offering
minimum interest of 3% and maximum
interest of 7.85% on FDs ranging from 7 days to 10 years. Here AAA
Bank
is offering different interest rates for different categories. So, in this table,
you can see the new interest rate of AAA Bank FD.
If you want to invest
your money in FD for 1 year  If you invest in fixed deposit, then
for general citizens it is 6.70 per annum and
for senior citizens this rate is a
little higher which is 7.20 per annum.
Now let us know further that if you invest
₹5000000 in fixed deposit of II Aaa Bank for 1 year, then
how much return will you get on it,
its calculation is very
simple, 500000 at 6.70 is
3350 and at 7.20 it is
3600, so if you invest ₹5000000
in fixed deposit of Iaa Bank for 1 year,
then general citizens will get ₹3350
interest and the total return will be
₹
3350 and if you are a senior citizen then you will
get ₹33600 interest and the total
return will be ₹
3600. By the way, if you invest in III Bank  The
longer you invest your money in a fixed deposit, the
higher the returns you will get. In this, you
get the benefit of compound interest. So,
if you
want to earn good returns by investing your money safely, then
III Bank FD i.e. fixed
deposit can be a best option. If
you liked this information, then share this video
with your friends and
for such information, definitely subscribe to this channel.